everyone this is ey on E censored
Supernatural Bible tunes on YouTube and
today is the 20th of January 2024 this
will be a quick book review for my one
of my latest books available on Amazon
it's called Castle's Duke and unicorn
Supernatural Bible changes this book
this small book 5.75 by 6 in covers over
300 King James Bible changes we're
seeing lines signs and wonders happen
right now our bibles are supernaturally
changing preparing the way for the
Antichrist and it really is unbelievable
the types of
language that we are now witnessing in
scripture he who read it let him
understand the Abomination or desolation
is taking place right now while the
church sleeps and I've been covering
these changes for over seven and a half
years on
YouTube here it is on Amazon on and
again this book has over 300 examples of
Bible changes correlated with a royal
mythological fairy tale including new
words such as castles Duke unicorns
damsels cockatrice seder dwarf and many
other new and multiplied
words our bibles are supernaturally
changing preparing the way for the
Antichrist and it's absolutely
diabolical
now I want to go ahead and
read um yeah let me go ahead and read
some um of these verses that I cover in
this book and I'm going to start here
with this is my manuscript 1st Samuel
17:22 says this today and David left his
carriage in the hand of The Keeper of
the carriage and ran into the army and
came and saluted his brethren
do you recognize any of that language
yeah neither do I let's look at another
[Music]
one uh let me just fast forward
here U yeah I'll read this one
too 1st Samuel 17:5 and he had in helmet
of brass upon his head and he was armed
with a coat of mail and the weight of
the coat was 5,000 shekels of
brass
here's another one 2 Chronicles 20:30 so
the realm of Jehoshaphat was quiet for
as God gave him rest
roundabout moving
ahead 1st Samuel 25:42 and Abigail
hasted and arose and rode upon an ass
with five damsels of hers that went
after her and she went after the
messengers of David and became his
wife
1 Samuel 28:3 now Samuel was dead and
all Israel had lamented him and buried
him in Rama even in his own City and
Saul had put away those that had
familiar spirits and the Wizards out of
the
land 1 Samuel 28:9 and the woman said
unto him behold th knowest what saath
done how he hath cut off those that have
familiar spirits and the Wizards out of
the land wherefore then layest thou a
snare for my life to cause me to
die I'm going to zoom forward catch
something else completely different like
this one 1 Thessalonians 2: 19 for what
is Our Hope or Joy or crown of rejoicing
are not even ye in the presence of our
Lord Jesus Christ at is
coming 2 Chronicles 22:10 but when
athalia the mother of aiah saw that her
son was dead she arose and destroyed all
the seed Royal of the house of Judah all
of
it 2 Chronicles 23:1 then they brought
out the King's son and put upon him the
crown and gave him the testimony and
made him King and JEA and his sons
anointed him and said God Save the King
do you recognize any of this
language I
don't 2 Chronicles 23:15 so they laid
hands on her and when she was come to
the entering of the horse gate by the
King's house they slew her
there here's another one 2 Chronicles
7:11 thus Solomon finished the house of
the Lord and the the King's house and
all that came to Solomon's heart to make
in the house of the Lord and in his own
house he Pro prosperously
affected and it goes on and on with
changes like this
one 2 Chronicles 12:20 instead of wh
instead of which king Ram made Shields
of brass and committed them to the hands
of the chief of the Guard they kept the
entrance of the King's house
I'm going to zoom ahead
here and let's look at uh this one 2
Kings 25:9 and he burnt the house of the
Lord and the King's house and all the
houses of Jerusalem and every great
man's house burnt he with
fire now as I'm sharing these with
you you're going to discern other new
words that didn't that don't relate to a
royal theme or mythological in nature
but you're going to see language that is
violent that is like a casting of spells
and these spells are manifesting
today do you understand there's an
Alchemy witchcraft spell that's going on
with the rewriting of scripture and it's
truly
diabolical and then again I have over
300 scripture verses here like this one
2 Kings 711 he called the porters and
they told it to the King's house with
him they're taking words out and they're
plopping words in that don't even make
any sense and we see thus on every
single page of the Bible from Genesis to
Revelations and everything in
between I want to try to find a
completely new verse for you like this
one 3D John 1 ver14 but I trust I shall
shortly see thee and we shall speak face
to face peace be to thee our friends
salute thee greet the Friends by name
there's a lot of saluting now in the
Bible this is as far as I'm going to go
again there over 300 scripture verses
that relate to the Royal mythological
agenda that we see popped into our
Bibles now I'm going to go back
to this and I want to show you these
other books that I've written that are
also available on Amazon
and the first two that I wrote are
really important because they they
basically create the foundation for my
other books and these two books the
first book the abomination of desolation
and Supernatural Bible changes covers
Bible changes thousands of Bible changes
and I start off by showing a toz new
words in the
Bible and I show other changes of
scripture and then the second book
Supernatural Bible changes I talk about
the various agendas that are being
plopped into scripture and I show the
scripture verse and even the Strong's
number for your further
research and then these other books
afterwards I talk about specific
subjects like Islamic language in the
Bible I talk about the ostor in the
Bible essentially the Antichrist is
rising you know the one who will pretend
that he is God according to 2
Thessalonians 2 this is what's happening
in the Bible Our God our creator is
being replaced in scripture with the
Antichrist the counterfeit God and if
you remember we learned in 2
Thessalonians 2 I'm paraphrasing that he
would pretend that he is God and there
would be a great falling away and this
is happening today because if you do not
see the Bible changes you are worshiping
the Beast it's that simple that
absolutely horrifying but absolutely
true this book right here Bible truth
and the strong delusion is an excellent
book it's a small book and it shows a
diverse array of Bible changes that you
could open up the book and read one
verse and the change should pop out at
you like popcorn and it's a great
resource to show anybody about the Bible
changes and then I also want to show you
my latest books right here all of these
are small books um that have a host
thousands of not thousands but all
collectively but show hundreds of Bible
changes according to themes like armies
of aliens you know illegal aliens or
outer space aliens pandemics plagues and
Supernatural Bible changes College
Matrix and looking glasses and this last
one castles Duke and unicorns you can't
make this up our bibles are becoming a
book of fables and it's time to wake up
in Jesus name be strong and courageous
brothers and sisters do not Fe
or be dismayed for the Lord your God is
with you wherever you go until next
time